USER ACCESS ANALYSIS:

SYSTEM USERS (Linux):
- Names like: root, daemon, www-data, mysql
- UID: 0-999
- Used for system services

REGULAR USERS:
- Names like: john, mary, sabat
- UID: 1000+
- Used for people

SECURITY RISKS:
If regular user has system groups:
- Can access sensitive files
- Can modify system settings
- Security breaches

EXAMPLE:
Regular user in 'sudo' group = Can run admin commands
Regular user in 'shadow' group = Can read passwords

SOLUTION:
- Give only needed permissions
- Regular user should not be in system groups
